That's for you.
هذا لك.
- Mmm! - So good!
- ممم! - جيد جدًا!
So good.
جيد جداً.
Hi, Matmat.
مرحباً، مطمت.
I'm not paying for what she ate.
أنا لا أدفع ثمن ما أكلته.
I want an older brother like you!
أريد أخًا أكبر مثلك!
Mia, let's go.
ميا، دعنا نذهب.
"Face your fears."
"واجه مخاوفك."
That's what you should be doing
هذا ما يجب عليك فعله
That way Patrick, will stop being affected
بهذه الطريقة، سيتوقف باتريك عن التأثر
because of your fear of butterflies.
بسبب خوفك من الفراشات.
And among all my books,
ومن بين جميع كتبي،
I really want this one to be published the most.
أريد حقًا أن يتم نشر هذا الكتاب أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
Because it's inspired by the three of us you, Matmat, and me.
لأنه مستوحى منا نحن الثلاثة ، أنت، ومتمات، وأنا.
Do it because the story is beautiful.
افعل ذلك لأن القصة جميلة.
And not because of us.
وليس بسببنا.
Our story is beautiful.
قصتنا جميلة.
Period.
فترة.
♪ Have you ever been A little afraid of love ♪
هل كنت خائفًا قليلاً من الحب يومًا؟
I hate kids.
أنا أكره الأطفال.
Most of those who buy your books are kids.
معظم الذين يشترون كتبك هم من الأطفال.
So, why do you hate them?
إذن، لماذا تكرههم؟
My books are for all.
كتبي للجميع.
It just so happens that kids love them.
لقد حدث أن الأطفال يحبونهم.
But why do you hate them?
ولكن لماذا تكرههم؟
They are loud, naughty, and always complaining.
إنهم صاخبون، ومشاكسون، ويشكون دائمًا.
They'd be like, "Mommy! Mommy, look at me!"
سيكونون مثل، "أمي! أمي، انظري إلي!"
"Love me! Love me!"
"أحبني! أحبني!"
"I need to be loved!"
"أنا بحاجة إلى أن أكون محبوبًا!"
I love them.
أنا أحبهم.
I love kids.
أنا أحب الأطفال.
Even though they are naughty,
على الرغم من أنهم شقيون،
your frustration will ease when they show you affection.
سوف يخف إحباطك عندما يظهرون لك المودة.
That's why it feels good to take care of them.
لهذا السبب أشعر بالسعادة عندما أهتم بهم.
It feels good to love them.
من الجميل أن نحبهم.
I don't want to have kids with you.
لا أريد أن أنجب أطفالاً منك.
Huh?
هاه؟
If that's how you'll treat our future kids,
إذا كانت هذه هي الطريقة التي ستعامل بها أطفالنا في المستقبل،
I don't want to. I'll just get jealous.
لا أريد ذلك. سأشعر بالغيرة فحسب.
- So, it's a no.
- إذن، الإجابة هي لا.
I'm not going to be the mother of your kids, Patrick.
لن أكون أم أطفالك، باتريك.
Mia?
ميا؟
Is this your way of convincing me?
هل هذه طريقتك لإقناعي؟
Don't you want a little Mia?
ألا تريد القليل من ميا؟
Or a little Patrick?
أو باتريك الصغير؟
If we were to have kids,
لو كان لدينا أطفال،
you wouldn't need to be jealous.
لا داعي لأن تشعر بالغيرة.
My heart is big enough that it can share all my love.
قلبي كبير بما فيه الكفاية بحيث يمكنه أن يشارك كل حبي.
My love for Matmat,
حبي لماتمات
for my future kids,
من أجل أطفالي في المستقبل،
and for you.
ولك.
Mm. It's beautiful, isn't it?
مممم، إنه جميل، أليس كذلك؟
I love you so much, Mommy!
أنا أحبك كثيرًا يا أمي!
Aw, you're so sweet, dear!
أوه، أنت لطيفة جدًا، عزيزتي!
I love you so much, Daddy!
انا احبك كثيرا يا أبي!
Aw, dear!
أوه عزيزي!
Aww!
أوووه!
Looks like you need more videos.
يبدو أنك بحاجة إلى المزيد من مقاطع الفيديو.
Are you my new manager?
هل أنت مديري الجديد؟
I just want to help Madeth.
أريد فقط مساعدة ماديث.
So she will have more options.
لذلك سيكون لديها المزيد من الخيارات.
Besides, this is for you.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، هذا لك.
I'll say yes if you become my new manager.
سأقول نعم إذا أصبحت مديري الجديد.
Mia, I'm a nurse aide, not a manager.
ميا، أنا مساعدة ممرضة، وليس مدير.
Look.
ينظر.
You still don't have a video of you writing.
ليس لديك فيديو لك أثناء الكتابة.
I might need to get a video of you writing at your desk.
ربما أحتاج إلى الحصول على فيديو لك وأنت تكتب على مكتبك.
But before we go home, let's go to the grocery store.
ولكن قبل أن نعود إلى المنزل، دعونا نذهب إلى متجر البقالة.
We no longer have food in the fridge since you and Matmat burned it all.
لم يعد لدينا طعام في الثلاجة منذ أن أحرقته أنت ومتمات بالكامل.
It's scary when you two get hungry. You might end up eating me.
إنه أمر مخيف عندما تشعران بالجوع. قد تأكلاني في النهاية.
Alright. I'm saying yes.
حسناً، أنا أقول نعم.
- Huh? - I want to have a kid with you.
- هاه؟ - أريد أن أنجب طفلاً منك.
Haven't you moved on from that?
ألم تتحرك من هذا الأمر؟
I just thought that if my kid takes after you,
لقد فكرت للتو أنه إذا كان طفلي يشبهك،
I wouldn't get jealous.
لا أريد أن أشعر بالغيرة.
Because I'd have two Patricks' to love me.
لأنه سيكون لدي اثنين من باتريك ليحبوني.
It's a win for me.
إنه فوز بالنسبة لي.
Come on, let's go home.
هيا لنذهب إلى المنزل.
Hey. I said yes.
مهلا، قلت نعم.
Patrick. I said I want a little Patrick.
باتريك. قلت أريد باتريك صغيرًا.
Patrick! Patrick, let's have a baby!
باتريك! باتريك، دعنا ننجب طفلاً!
You're too loud. It's embarrassing.
صوتك عالي جدًا، إنه أمر محرج.
I'll update you once the plane lands.
سأوافيكم بالتحديثات بمجرد هبوط الطائرة.
And I'll message you every day so you won't feel like I left.
وسأرسل لك رسالة كل يوم حتى لا تشعر وكأنني غادرت.
So, he just said that?
إذن فهو قال ذلك للتو؟
But he won't actually do it?
ولكنه لن يفعل ذلك فعليا؟
Lucky you, getting a second chance at a love life.
أنت محظوظ، حصلت على فرصة ثانية لحياة حب.
Doc, good thing you and your ex-girlfriend got back together!
يا دكتور، من حسن الحظ أنك وصديقتك السابقة عدتم لبعضكم البعض!
You're so lucky.
أنت محظوظ جدًا.
She's no longer my ex.
إنها لم تعد حبيبتي السابقة.
'Cause she's my girlfriend again.
لأنها صديقتي مرة أخرى.
Okay. Okay.
حسنًا. حسنًا.
Good thing she came back to you.
من الجيد أنها عادت إليك.
Because if it was me, Doc,
لأنه لو كنت أنا، يا دكتور،
our breakup would be the last time we'd ever see each other.
إن انفصالنا سيكون المرة الأخيرة التي سنرى فيها بعضنا البعض.
Yeah, Doc. Why did you two break up?
نعم يا دكتور، لماذا انفصلتم؟
I was so busy with medical school then,
لقد كنت مشغولاً جدًا بكلية الطب حينها،
and she was busy with her business.
وكانت مشغولة بأعمالها.
There was no cheating involved. We broke up on good terms.
لم يكن هناك أي غش. انفصلنا بسلام.
We just didn't have much time for each other.
لم يكن لدينا الكثير من الوقت لبعضنا البعض.
You two were okay and on good terms?
هل كنتم بخير وعلى علاقة جيدة؟
Mm!
مم!
They broke up two years ago!
لقد انفصلا منذ عامين!
But even though they've broken up,
ولكن على الرغم من أنهم انفصلوا،
they are still on good terms!
لا زالوا على علاقة جيدة!
Because Miss Erica is so kind!
لأن الآنسة إيريكا لطيفة جدًا!
She's really kind.
إنها لطيفة حقا.
Miss Li, Miss Erica is also sweet!
آنسة لي، آنسة إيريكا لطيفة أيضًا!
- Oh, sweet! - She's so sweet!
- أوه، حلوة! - إنها حلوة جدًا!
That must be so sweet, Doc.
يجب أن يكون هذا لطيفًا جدًا، يا دكتور.
As they say,
كما يقولون،
love is sweeter the second time around. Right, Doc?
الحب أحلى في المرة الثانية. صحيح يا دكتور؟
Uh, meaning?
اه، ما معنى؟
You still loved her even when you two parted ways?
هل مازلت تحبها حتى عندما افترقتم؟
For me, I never stopped loving her.
أما أنا فلم أتوقف عن حبها أبدًا.
She was my first love.
لقد كانت حبي الأول.
Dear, it's not easy to move on from your first love.
عزيزي، ليس من السهل المضي قدمًا من حبك الأول.
That's where we get to experience
هذا هو المكان الذي نحصل فيه على الخبرة
how sweet or painful love is.
كم هو الحب حلو أو مؤلم
Mmm.
ممم.
Mia.
لي.
You said we'd talk again when we got home.
قلت أننا سوف نتحدث مرة أخرى عندما نعود إلى المنزل.
Yes. But I didn't say we needed to hug.
نعم، ولكنني لم أقل أننا بحاجة إلى العناق.
You didn't say we couldn't do it.
لم تقل أننا لا نستطيع فعل ذلك.
Patpat?
يلزق؟
Patpat!
يلزق!
Matmat is home!
مطمت هو المنزل!
Mia, Matmat is home.
ميا، ماتمات في المنزل.
I'm not letting you go until you agree to talk in my room later.
لن أسمح لك بالرحيل حتى توافق على التحدث في غرفتي لاحقًا.
Mm? Patpat!
مم؟ عصا!
M-Mia!
م-لي!
Mia, come on, let go of me.
ميا، تعالي، دعيني أذهب.
Matmat! We're in here!
مطمات! نحن هنا!
Mia!
لي!
Where?
أين؟
- Mia, stop. - Where is Patpat, Mia?
- ميا، توقفي. - أين باتبات، ميا؟
- Mia, please! - We'll talk in my room later.
- ميا، من فضلك! - سنتحدث في غرفتي لاحقًا.
We'll have wine, cheese, and more.
سيكون لدينا النبيذ والجبن وأكثر من ذلك.
Please let me go.
من فضلك دعني أذهب.
We're here, Matmat--
نحن هنا، ماتمات--
- We're in the kitchen! - Are you with Patpat?
- نحن في المطبخ! - هل أنت مع باتبات؟
Yes, he's here!
نعم إنه هنا!
Alright! I'm saying yes!
حسناً! أنا أقول نعم!
Say it. Don't be unfair.
قلها، لا تكن غير عادل.
We'll talk in your room later.
سنتحدث في غرفتك لاحقًا.
- With? - With cheese! With wine!
- مع؟ - مع الجبن! مع النبيذ!
And?
و؟
- And more! - And more?
- و أكثر! - و أكثر؟
- Come on. - Aw, little Pat--
- هيا. - أوه، يا بات الصغيرة--
- Patpat. - I'll take it.
- باتبات. - سآخذها.
M-Matmat kept calling your name, but you weren't responding.
استمر م-ماتمات في مناداتك باسمك، لكنك لم تكن تستجيب.
What are you going to do?
ما كنت تنوي القيام به؟
- Uh… - Are you going to talk?
- اه... - هل ستتحدث؟
Can Matmat join you?
هل يمكن لماتمات أن ينضم إليكم؟
Matmat, I bought new art materials for you.
مطمت، لقد اشتريت لك أدوات فنية جديدة.
- New coloring materials… - Wow! Wow!
- مواد تلوين جديدة... - واو! واو!
Uh, Madeth.
أوه، ماديث.
Are you talking with someone?
هل تتحدث مع شخص ما؟
Uh…
أوه…
I'm not.
انا لست كذلك.
I'm just watching videos because I need to finish this
أنا فقط أشاهد الفيديوهات لأنني بحاجة إلى إنهاء هذا
'A day in the life of a writer' project.
مشروع يوم في حياة كاتب.
I see. It's your new endorsement with Vincent, right?
فهمت. هذا تأييدك الجديد مع فينسنت، صحيح؟
Correct! Yes! Exactly.
صحيح! نعم! بالضبط.
Boss V called.
اتصل الرئيس V.
He said Miss Erica is already asking for the video.
وقال إن الآنسة إيريكا تطلب الفيديو بالفعل.
I told him I'm still working on it.
قلت له أنني لا أزال أعمل على ذلك.
So you've spoken to him?
هل تحدثت معه؟
Yeah. He was with Miss Erica when he called.
نعم. كان مع الآنسة إيريكا عندما اتصل.
He called Madeth but didn't bother to message me.
لقد اتصل بماديث لكنه لم يكلف نفسه عناء إرسال رسالة لي.
What did you just say, sis?
ماذا قلت للتو يا أختي؟
Huh? Nothing. I said that endorsement seems important.
هاه؟ لا شيء. قلتُ إنَّ هذا التأييد يبدو مهمًا.
Vincent even spent the day with your client.
حتى أن فينسنت أمضى اليوم مع عميلك.
So tell me…
فأخبرني...
Are you saying that she's missing me?
هل تقول أنها تفتقدني؟
She didn't directly say it, Boss V.
لم تقل ذلك بشكل مباشر، يا رئيس V.
But I just have a gut feeling.
لكن لدي شعور غريزي فقط.
Madeth, I'm not sure your gut feeling should be trusted.
ماديث، أنا لست متأكدة من أن حدسك يمكن الوثوق به.
Then why did you hire me for this job, Boss V?
إذن لماذا وظفتني لهذه الوظيفة يا رئيس V؟
Trust me, Boss V.
ثق بي يا رئيس V.
Just a little push,
فقط دفعة صغيرة
Gemma will eventually verbalize that she misses you.
في النهاية سوف تقول جيما أنها تفتقدك.
Sure, sure. I'll call her right now.
بالتأكيد، بالتأكيد. سأتصل بها الآن.
Hey! No, Boss V!
مهلا! لا، يا رئيس V!
Don't! Don't call her yet!
لا تفعل! لا تتصل بها بعد!
Why? What if Gemma is upset because I haven't text her?
لماذا؟ ماذا لو كانت جيما منزعجة لأني لم أرسل لها رسالة؟
Oh, Boss V.
أوه، الرئيس V.
Haven't you heard of delayed gratification?
هل سمعت عن الإشباع المؤجل؟
Just wait for my signal. I'll tell you when it's time.
انتظر إشارتي فقط. سأخبرك عندما يحين الوقت.
So what? You're the boss now?
ماذا إذن؟ أنت الرئيس الآن؟
I'm the one getting orders from you now?
أنا من يتلقى الأوامر منك الآن؟
Vincent.
فينسينت.
Miss Erica?
آنسة إيريكا؟
Boss V, is that Miss Erica?
الرئيس V، هل هذه الآنسة إيريكا؟
- Hi!
-ه ...
- Hi! Hello! - Erica!
- أهلاً! أهلاً! - إيريكا!
Boss V?
الرئيس الخامس؟
Oh, sorry. I got a little excited.
أوه، آسف. لقد أصبحت متحمسًا قليلاً.
Really? We've been talking on the phone for a while.
حقاً؟ لقد كنا نتحدث على الهاتف لفترة.
No, but it's different seeing you in person.
لا، ولكن الأمر يختلف عندما أراك شخصيًا.
Oh, yeah. Um…
أوه نعم. أم...
- Let's have a seat. - Yeah.
- دعنا نجلس. - نعم.
Uh, Miss!
أوه، آنسة!
Good to see you. How are you?
يسعدني رؤيتك. كيف حالك؟
I'm good. I'm good and I'm happy to see you as well.
أنا بخير. أنا بخير وسعيد برؤيتك أيضًا.
Uh, yes. We'll order, please.
نعم، سنطلب، من فضلك.
Okay. Uh…
حسنًا. اه...
Patpat,
يلزق،
Dr. Anok said
وقال الدكتور أنوك
in different countries the butterfly is a cure.
في بلدان مختلفة تعتبر الفراشة علاجًا.
Cure…
دواء…
What does that mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
Does the illness go away?
هل يزول المرض؟
Is it like…
هل هو مثل...
If you could drink the butterfly
إذا كان بإمكانك شرب الفراشة
then you'll be healed.
ثم سوف تشفى.
It's not a drug, Matmat.
إنه ليس دواء، مطمت.
What doc meant was,
ما قصده الطبيب هو،
the butterflies…
الفراشات…
are a symbol of healing.
هي رمز للشفاء.
Remember, they were caterpillars first
تذكر أنهم كانوا يرقات أولاً
before they became butterflies.
قبل أن يصبحوا فراشات.
They're like dinosaurs.
إنهم مثل الديناصورات.
They start out as babies then they grow old.
إنهم يبدأون كأطفال ثم يكبرون.
Could be.
ربما يكون.
Like an Archaeopteryx.
مثل الأركيوبتركس.
First bird dinosaur.
أول طائر ديناصور.
But they're born with wings already, Patpat.
لكنهم ولدوا بأجنحة بالفعل، باتبات.
What I'm trying to say is,
ما أحاول قوله هو،
the butterflies' wings and how they fly freely
أجنحة الفراشات وكيف تطير بحرية
symbolize that a person has healed.
يرمز إلى شفاء الشخص.
The illness is gone?
هل ذهب المرض؟
Free from the pain.
خالية من الألم.
Doc said,
قال الطبيب
Patpat is also getting affected because…
باتبات يتأثر أيضًا بسبب ...
Because Matmat is scared of butterflies.
لأن مطماطة تخاف من الفراشات.
Are you scared of butterflies too, Patpat?
هل أنت خائف من الفراشات أيضًا يا باتبات؟
Not really, Matmat.
ليس حقا، مطمت.
But…
لكن…
I also have to move places,
يجب علي أيضًا الانتقال إلى أماكن أخرى،
even though I'm not the one being chased by the butterflies.
رغم أنني لست الشخص الذي تطارده الفراشات.
That's why we should face our fears.
ولهذا السبب يجب علينا أن نواجه مخاوفنا.
We should face our fears so we don't have to move.
ينبغي علينا أن نواجه مخاوفنا حتى لا نضطر إلى التحرك.
Do you think…
هل تعتقد…
you can do that?
هل تستطيع فعل ذلك؟
Do you think you can face your fear of butterflies?
هل تعتقد أنك قادر على مواجهة خوفك من الفراشات؟
We have new bread.
لدينا خبز جديد.
To replace what Mia burnt.
لتعويض ما أحرقته ميا.
Zelda?
زيلدا؟
Do you know where you are?
هل تعرف أين أنت؟
Isolation room.
غرفة العزل.
Do you know how you got here?
هل تعلم كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟
Mm-hmm.
مممم.
I walked here.
لقد مشيت هنا.
Did you go to Mia's house?
هل ذهبت إلى بيت ميا؟
Y-Yes.
ن-نعم.
I wished her a happy birthday.
تمنيت لها عيد ميلاد سعيدًا.
Did she help you to go there?
هل ساعدتك على الذهاب إلى هناك؟
No, no. I was alone when I went out.
لا، لا. كنت وحدي عندما خرجت.
And then…
وثم…
He thought I was her.
لقد ظن أنني هي.
He thought I was her!
لقد ظن أنني هي!
Who?
من؟
Who did they think you were?
من ظنوا أنك؟
Ingrid.
إنغريد.
He thought I was Ingrid Hernandez.
ظن أنني إنغريد هيرنانديز.
I'm not her.
أنا لست هي.
I'm not, I'm not Ingrid.
أنا لست، أنا لست إنغريد.
Ingrid?
إنغريد؟
Mia's mom?
أم ميا؟
I'm not her.
أنا لست هي.
- Do you know who he was? - No.
- هل تعرف من هو؟ - لا.
I don't know him.
انا لا اعرفه
His face…
وجهه…
He was so mad!
لقد كان غاضبا جدا!
So, so mad!
مجنون جداً!
He thought I was Ingrid!
لقد ظن أنني إنغريد!
He thought I was Ingrid but that's not me!
لقد ظن أنني إنغريد ولكن هذه ليست أنا!
That's not me!
هذا ليس انا!
He wants to kill me! I don't want to die!
يريد قتلي! لا أريد أن أموت!
I don't want to die!
لا أريد أن أموت!
Do you think she's telling the truth?
هل تعتقد أنها تقول الحقيقة؟
Do you believe that's what happened to her?
هل تعتقد أن هذا ما حدث لها؟
That she was mistaken as Mia's mother?
أنها أخطأت كأم ميا؟
Okay, calm down. You're safe, you're safe.
حسناً، اهدأ. أنت بأمان، أنت بأمان.
If it's true that someone kidnapped her,
إذا كان صحيحا أن أحدهم اختطفها،
because they thought she was Ingrid,
لأنهم ظنوا أنها إنغريد،
Could Samuel and Mia be in danger too?
هل من الممكن أن يكون صموئيل وميا في خطر أيضًا؟
Are you saying, Doc,
هل تقول يا دكتور؟
that there's someone out there
أن هناك شخص ما هناك
who is a threat to their lives?
من يشكل تهديدا على حياتهم؟
Not just that.
ليس هذا فقط.
What if they're looking for Ingrid
ماذا لو كانوا يبحثون عن إنغريد؟
because she's still alive?
لأنها لا تزال على قيد الحياة؟
What if Ingrid is still really alive?
ماذا لو كانت إنغريد لا تزال على قيد الحياة حقًا؟
Then it's going to change everybody's lives.
ومن ثم سيتغير حياة الجميع.
Maybe it'll be better if she comes back.
ربما سيكون الأمر أفضل إذا عادت.
Because then…
لأنه حينها…
there will be no more mystery.
لن يكون هناك المزيد من الغموض.
No more hiding.
لا مزيد من الاختباء.
Is it true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Are you really going to return to your family, Ingrid?
هل ستعودين حقا إلى عائلتك يا إنغريد؟
Mia.
لي.
Come in.
ادخل.
Hello, pretty boy.
مرحباً أيها الصبي الجميل.
Wine.
خمر.
Cheese.
جبن.
And more.
و أكثر.
Matmat told me something earlier.
لقد أخبرني مطمت بشيء في وقت سابق.
He and Dr. Anok talked.
وتحدث هو والدكتور أنوك.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Wine and cheese.
النبيذ والجبن.
Let's talk.
دعونا نتحدث.
Wine, cheese and more.
النبيذ والجبن وأكثر من ذلك.
Me. I'm the "and more."
أنا. أنا "وأكثر".
Really?
حقًا؟
You really know how to kill the mood.
أنت حقا تعرف كيف تقتل المزاج.
Are we really going to talk about Matmat?
هل سنتحدث فعلاً عن مطمات؟
Well, what are we going to talk about?
حسنًا، ما الذي سنتحدث عنه؟
Us.
نحن.
There's so much we can talk about and do.
هناك الكثير مما يمكننا التحدث عنه والقيام به.
So please, let's not talk about Matmat right now.
لذا من فضلك، دعنا لا نتحدث عن ماتمات الآن.
Every time you mention Matmat,
في كل مرة تذكر فيها مطمت،
you have to drink a glass of wine.
يجب عليك شرب كأس من النبيذ.
Fine.
بخير.
But you drink a glass
لكنك تشرب كأسا
every time you curse or say something mean.
في كل مرة تلعن أو تقول شيئا سيئا.
That's all?
هذا كل شئ؟
Fine. Deal.
حسناً، اتفقنا.
I'm not Gemma, I shouldn't be this drunk, this fast.
أنا لست جيما، لا ينبغي لي أن أكون في حالة سُكر أو سرعة كهذه.
Don't drag other people into this.
لا تجر أشخاصًا آخرين إلى هذا.
Your drunk because you drank too much.
أنت في حالة سكر لأنك شربت كثيرًا.
I'm sure you love that we're talking about her.
أنا متأكد من أنك تحب أننا نتحدث عنها.
Leave Gemma out of it. Come here, you're talking too much.
دع جيما خارج الموضوع. تعالي هنا، أنت تتكلمين كثيرًا.
You really just want attention, huh?
أنت حقا تريد فقط الاهتمام، أليس كذلك؟
Mm-hmm.
مممم.
I'm so happy, even just like this.
أنا سعيدة جدًا، حتى بهذه الطريقة.
I'm so, so happy…
أنا سعيدة جدًا جدًا
that you and Matmat are living here with me.
أنك ومتمات تعيشان هنا معي.
So happy…
سعيدة جداً…
I'm so very, very happy.
أنا سعيد جدًا جدًا.
Me too.
أنا أيضاً.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
"I'LL BE BACK"
"سأعود"
She's the only one who could've put this here.
إنها الوحيدة التي كان بإمكانها وضع هذا هنا.
Look at this!
أنظر إلى هذا!
- You did this to yourself! - Ahh!
- لقد فعلت هذا بنفسك! - آه!
- Hey!
- يا!
I've waited for this moment for a long time.
لقد انتظرت هذه اللحظة لفترة طويلة.
- No! I'm not Ingrid!
- لا! أنا لست إنغريد!
- No! - Shut up!
- لا! - اسكت!
Everyone thinks you're dead.
الجميع يظن أنك ميت.
I'm then only one who saw you come out of the lake.
أنا الوحيد الذي رأى خروجك من البحيرة.
I'm not Ingrid!
أنا لست انغريد!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
آه! آه! آه!
Zelda!
زيلدا!
Nurse… Nurse… Nurse…
ممرضة... ممرضة... ممرضة...
Call my brother!
اتصل بأخي!
I'm leaving! I don't want to stay here anymore!
سأرحل! لا أريد البقاء هنا بعد الآن!
Transfer me to another hospital!
انقلي إلى مستشفى آخر!
"I'LL BE BACK"
"سأعود"
Miss Zelda!
آنسة زيلدا!
Miss Zelda, there's something I need to ask you, before you leave.
آنسة زيلدا، هناك شيء أريد أن أسألك عنه قبل أن تغادري.
Patrick, I'm about to leave.
باتريك، أنا على وشك المغادرة.
You went to Mia's mansion, right?
لقد ذهبت إلى قصر ميا، أليس كذلك؟
Were you the one who left the butterfly?
هل أنت الذي ترك الفراشة؟
We need to leave.
نحن بحاجة إلى المغادرة.
The letter? Was it from you?
الرسالة؟ هل كانت منك؟
- Yes, I put it there. - Auntie.
- نعم، لقد وضعته هناك. - عمتي.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
You put it there.
وضعته هناك.
Why did you do that?
لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
I put it there
لقد وضعته هناك
because someone told me to.
لأن أحدهم أخبرني بذلك.
Who?
من؟
I received some letters out of nowhere,
لقد تلقيت بعض الرسائل من العدم،
with instructions to give them to someone.
مع تعليمات لإعطائها لشخص ما.
Was it Ingrid Hernandez?
هل كانت إنغريد هيرنانديز؟
I'm a fan.
أنا من المعجبين.
I'm a big, big fan of Ingrid Hernandez.
أنا من المعجبين بشدة بإنغريد هيرنانديز.
I know everything about her
انا اعرف كل شيء عنها
because of the stories she wrote.
بسبب القصص التي كتبتها.
So, yes.
إذن نعم.
Everything was from Ingrid.
كل شيء كان من إنغريد.
And she's alive, Patrick.
وهي على قيد الحياة، باتريك.
She's alive!
إنها على قيد الحياة!
And if there's one thing I know for sure,
وإذا كان هناك شيء واحد أعرفه على وجه اليقين،
she's here, inside the hospital.
إنها هنا، داخل المستشفى.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
What makes a person want to run away?
ما الذي يجعل الإنسان يرغب في الهروب؟
What if Matmat gets chased by the butterflies?
ماذا لو تمت مطاردة مطمات من قبل الفراشات؟
They continue to face challenges daily.
ويستمرون في مواجهة التحديات اليومية.
Are you still afraid?
هل مازلت خائفة؟
I'm going to fight the butterflies.
سأقاتل الفراشات.
Your brother will fight too.
أخوك سوف يقاتل أيضاً
Are you ready to tell me what you saw?
هل أنت مستعد لتخبرني بما رأيت؟
I saw…
لقد رأيت…
What did you see the night our mother was murdered?
ماذا رأيت في الليلة التي قُتلت فيها والدتنا؟